Finding Aid for Board of Regents (University of Michigan) Records 1817-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibits of the Regents Meetings, 1899-1987
  - 1942-1951
    - June 11, 1943 (Box 51)
      - C-I2 (Box 51)
    - July 30, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 51)
      - E-Q (Box 51)
      - R-U4 (Box 51)
    - August 27, 1943 (Box 51)
    - September 24, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 51)
      - F-Q2 (Box 51)
    - October 23, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-N (Box 51)
      - O (Box 51)
      - P-F3 (Box 51)
    - November 27, 1943 (Box 52)
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 52)
      - P-G3 (Box 52)
      - H3-1/2-V3 (Box 52)
    - December 29, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 52)
      - F-X2 (Box 52)
    - January 28, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 52)
      - I-B3 (Box 52)
    - March 10, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 52)
      - H-H3 (Box 52)
    - April 21, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-D1/2 (Box 52)
      - E-H3 (Box 52)
    - May 26, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 52)
      - F-M2 (Box 52)
      - N2-X3 (Box 52)
    - June 12, 1944 (Box 53)
    - August 4, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 53)
      - H-N (Box 53)
      - O-I4 (Box 53)
    - September 16, 1944 (Box 53)
    - October 14, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 53)
      - F-K (Box 53)
      - L-J3 (Box 53)
    - November 11, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 53)
      - G (Box 53)
      - H-K3 (Box 53)
    - December 29, 1944
      - Draft Minutes and A-T (Box 53)
      - U-D2 (Box 53)
      - E2-Q4 (Box 53)
    - January 26, 1945 (Box 54)
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 54)
      - F-X2 (Box 54)
    - February 23, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 54)
      - N-F3 (Box 54)
    - March 30, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 54)
      - P-H3 (Box 54)
    - April 26, 1945 (Box 54)
    - May 25, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 54)
      - J-M3 (Box 54)
    - June 23, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 54)
      - Q-G3 (Box 54)
    - July 27, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 54)
      - L-N3 (Box 54)
    - August 31, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 54)
      - M-C3 (Box 54)
    - September 28, 1945 (Box 55)
    - October 20, 1945 (Box 55)
    - November 3, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-B (Box 55)
      - C-F (Box 55)
      - G-D2 (Box 55)
      - E2-Y3 (Box 55)
    - November 30, 1945
      - Draft Minutes and A-V (Box 55)
      - W-E3 (Box 55)
    - January 4, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 55)
      - N-T (Box 55)
      - U-O3 (Box 55)
    - February 1, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 55)
      - M-Z2 (Box 55)
    - February 22, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 55)
      - H-G3 (Box 55)
    - March 15, 1946 (Box 55)
    - March 29, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 55)
      - J-G3 (Box 55)
    - April 26, 1946 (Box 56)
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 56)
      - Q-S2 (Box 56)
    - May 31, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-B (Box 56)
      - C-N (Box 56)
      - O-L3 (Box 56)
    - June 12, 1946 (Box 56)
    - June 21, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-N (Box 56)
      - O-H3 (Box 56)
    - July 26, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 56)
      - J-K2 (Box 56)
      - L2-D4 (Box 56)
    - September 7, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 56)
      - K-Q (Box 56)
      - R-L3 (Box 56)
    - September 27, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 56)
      - K-N2 (Box 56)
    - October 25, 1946 (Box 57)
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 57)
      - J-Y2 (Box 57)
    - November 16, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 57)
      - K-S2 (Box 57)
    - December 27, 1946
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 57)
      - H-R (Box 57)
      - S-D2 (Box 57)
      - E2-X3 (Box 57)
      - Audit of Accounts (Supplement) (Box 57)
    - January 24, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 57)
      - I-T2 (Box 57)
    - February 28, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-N (Box 57)
      - O-E2 (Box 57)
      - F2-B4 (Box 57)
    - March 28, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 57)
      - Q-Y2 (Box 57)
    - April 25, 1947 (Box 58)
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 58)
      - G-V (Box 58)
      - W-H3 (Box 58)
    - June 13, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 58)
      - F-D2 (Box 58)
      - E2-M3 (Box 58)
      - N3-U6 (Box 58)
    - July 25, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 58)
      - F-Q (Box 58)
      - R-G4 (Box 58)
    - September 26, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 58)
      - G-L (Box 58)
      - M-K3 (Box 58)
      - L3-W4 (Box 58)
      - Exhibit D, Report of Ernst and Ernst of Audit for year ended, June 30, 1946 (Box 58)
    - October 24, 1947 (Box 59)
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 59)
      - D-N (Box 59)
      - O-Q2-1/2 (Box 59)
    - November 22, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 59)
      - H-X2 (Box 59)
    - December 19, 1947
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 59)
      - K-L (Box 59)
      - M-O3 (Box 59)
    - January 30, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 59)
      - I-L2 (Box 59)
      - M2-L4 (Box 59)
    - March 5, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 59)
      - G-S (Box 59)
      - T-D4 (Box 59)
    - April 2, 1948 (Box 60)
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 60)
      - K-H3 (Box 60)
    - May 1, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 60)
      - J-M3 (Box 60)
    - June 11, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 60)
      - F-W (Box 60)
      - X-G2 (Box 60)
      - H2-Z4 (Box 60)
    - July 16, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 60)
      - K-K3 (Box 60)
    - September 24, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 60)
      - E-P (Box 60)
      - Q-M3 (Box 60)
      - N3-F5 (Box 60)
    - October 16, 1948 (Box 61)
      - Draft Minutes and A-N (Box 61)
      - O-Y2 (Box 61)
      - Exhibit V2, Report of Ernst and Ernst of Audit for year ended, June 30, 1948 (Box 61)
    - November 13, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 61)
      - J-W2 (Box 61)
    - December 18, 1948
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 61)
      - J-Z (Box 61)
      - A2-L3 (Box 61)
    - January 29, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 61)
      - H-U3 (Box 61)
    - February 26, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 61)
      - L-F3 (Box 61)
    - March 26, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-N (Box 61)
      - O-Q3 (Box 61)
    - April 30, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 61)
      - K-S2 (Box 61)
    - May 20, 1949 (Box 62)
    - June 10, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 62)
      - I-R2 (Box 62)
    - July 20, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 62)
      - J-E2 (Box 62)
      - F2-U3 (Box 62)
    - September 24, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 62)
      - D-M (Box 62)
      - N-Y2 (Box 62)
      - Z2-A4 (Box 62)
    - November 5, 1949
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 62)
      - F-Q (Box 62)
      - R-E4 (Box 62)
      - Report of Ernst and Ernst of Audit for year ended, June 30, 1949 (Box 62)
    - November 19, 1949 (Box 62)
    - December 16, 1949 (Box 63)
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 63)
      - H-L (Box 63)
      - M-P (Box 63)
      - Q-I3 (Box 63)
    - January 20, 1959
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 63)
      - I-T2 (Box 63)
    - February 24, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 63)
      - D-S (Box 63)
      - T-J3 (Box 63)
    - March 18, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 63)
      - H-Q2 (Box 63)
    - April 18, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 63)
      - P-A3 (Box 63)
    - May 20, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 63)
      - M-C2 (Box 63)
      - D2-U3 (Box 63)
    - June 16, 1950 (Box 64)
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 64)
      - I-Q (Box 64)
      - R-U3 (Box 64)
    - June 26, July 8, 1950 (Box 64)
    - August 19, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 64)
      - G-U (Box 64)
      - V-Q4 (Box 64)
    - September 22, 1950 (Box 64)
    - September 30, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 64)
      - E-N2 (Box 64)
    - October 20, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 64)
      - G-L2 (Box 64)
    - November 18, 1950
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 64)
      - K-C3 (Box 64)
    - December 16, 1950 (Box 65)
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 65)
      - L (Box 65)
      - M-D3 (Box 65)
    - January 19, 1951 (Box 65)
    - February 15, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 65)
      - J-I2 (Box 65)
      - J2-M3 (Box 65)
    - March 16, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 65)
      - J-E3 (Box 65)
    - April 21, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 65)
      - L-K3 (Box 65)
    - May 19 and 21, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 65)
      - J-May 21, Exhibit A (Box 65)
    - June 15, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-0 (Box 65)
      - P-Q (Box 65)
      - R-J3 (Box 65)
    - June 29, 1951 (Box 66)
    - August 3, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 66)
      - H-L (Box 66)
      - M-F3 (Box 66)
    - August 22, 1951 (Box 66)
    - September 7, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 66)
      - F-V (Box 66)
      - W-G2 (Box 66)
    - September 28, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 66)
      - J-S2 (Box 66)
      - Exhibit Q2-1/2, Report of Ernst and Ernst of Audit for year ended, June 30, 1951 (Box 66)
    - October 26, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 66)
      - G-V2 (Box 66)
    - November 23, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 66)
      - J-Q2 (Box 66)
    - December 21, 1951
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 66)
      - I-J (Box 66)
      - K-W2 (Box 66)
  - 1952-1960
    - January-July 1952 (Box 74)
    - September 1952-March 1953 (Box 75)
    - April-October 1953 (Box 76)
    - November 1953-May 1954 (Box 77)
    - June-December 1954 (Box 78)
    - January-June 1955 (Box 79)
    - July-December 1955 (Box 80)
    - January-May 1956 (Box 81)
    - June-October 1956 (Box 82)
    - November 1956-April 1957 (Box 83)
    - May-September 1957 (Box 84)
    - October 1957-February 1958 (Box 85)
    - March-July 1958 (Box 86)
    - September 1958-January 1959 (Box 87)
    - February-June 1959 (Box 88)
    - July-December 1959 (Box 89)
    - January-June 1960 (Box 90)
    - July-December 1960 (Box 91)
  - 1961-1965
    - January-June 1961 (Box 93)
    - July-December 1961 (Box 94)
    - January-May 1962 (Box 95)
    - June-October 1962 (Box 96)
    - November 1962-March 1963 (Box 97)
    - April-June 1963 (Box 98)
    - July-December 1963 (Box 99)
    - December 1963-April 1964 (Box 100)
    - June-July 1964 (Box 101)
    - September-December 1964 (Box 102)
    - January-April 1965 (Box 103)
    - May-July 1965 (Box 104)
    - September-December 1965 (Box 105)
  - 1966-1967
    - January 1966-March 1966 (Box 112)
    - April 1966-June 1966 (Box 113)
    - July 1966-September 1966 (Box 114)
    - October 1966-January 1967 (Box 115)
    - February 1967-May 1967 (Box 116)
    - June 1967-September 1967 (Box 117)
    - October 1967-December 1967 (Box 118)
  - 1968-1977
    - January 1968-April 1968 (Box 121)
    - May 1968-September 1968 (Box 122)
    - October 1968-December 1968 (Box 123)
    - January 1969-June 1969 (Box 124)
    - July 1969-December 1969 (Box 125)
    - January 1970-June 1970 (Box 126)
    - July 1970-December 1970 (Box 127)
    - January 1971-June 1971 (Box 128)
    - July 1971-December 1971 (Box 129)
    - January 1972-June 1972 (Box 130)
    - July 1972-December 1972 (Box 131)
    - January 1973-June 1973 (Box 132)
    - July 1973-December 1973 (Box 133)
    - January 1974-June 1974 (Box 134)
    - July 1974-January 1975 (Box 135)
    - February 1975-May 1975 (Box 136)
    - June 1975-October 1975 (Box 137)
    - November 1975-May 1976 (Box 138)
    - June 1976-October 1976 (Box 139)
    - November 1976-May 1977 (Box 140)
  - 1977-1980
    - June 1977-October 1977 (Box 143)
    - November 1977-June 1978 (Box 144)
    - July 1978-October 1978 (Box 145)
    - November 1978-April 1979 (Box 146)
    - May 1979-September 1979 (Box 147)
    - September 1979-April 1980 (Box 148)
    - May 1980-June 1980 (Box 149)
    - September 1980-December 1980 (Box 150)
  - 1981-1987
    - January 1981-June 1981 (Box 153)
    - July 1981-December 1981 (Box 154)
    - January 1982-May 1982 (Box 155)
    - May 1982-October 1982 (Box 156)
    - October 1982-March 1983 (Box 157)
    - April 1983-June 1983 (Box 158)
    - July 1983-October 1983 (Box 159)
    - November 1983-April 1984 (Box 160)
    - May 1984-October 1984 (Box 162)
    - November 1984-February 1985 (Box 163)
    - March 1985-June 1985 (Box 164)
    - August 1985-October 1985 (Box 165)
    - November 1985-February 1986 (Box 166)
    - March 1986-May 1986 (Box 167)
    - June 1986-September 1986 (Box 168)
    - September 1986-December 1986 (Box 169)
    - January 1987-May 1987 (Box 170)
    - May 1987-September 1987 (Box 171)
    - September 1987-December 1987 (Box 172)
    - January 1988-April 1988 (Box 182)
    - May 1988-July 1988 (Box 183)
    - September 1988-November 1988 (Box 184)
    - December 1988- (Box 185)
- Topical File
  The Topical Files series an artificially created alphabet of materials drawn from various sources pertaining to the work of the Board of Regents. There are several subseries chronologically bounded of Topical files (1817-1970, 1949-1969, 1976-1983, 1958-1999) reflecting various accessions of material. There may be some overlap of between subseries.
  Among the most significant topics in the 1817-1970 subseries is a large body of papers relating to the Douglas-Rose controversy--concerning a deficit in the accounts of the chemical laboratory, ca. 1875-1880. Other material of note includes 1928 file relating to the founding dates of the university and the presidential search of 1925.
  Later additions to the series cover a wide range of the regent's business including extensive files on the revision of the Regent's by-laws.
  - 1817-1970, 1867-1928
    - Auditor's Reports, 1896-1902; 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Committee Reports
      - Undated, 1871; 1880-1881; 1924 (Box 44)
      - Recommending a salary change for acting president Henry Frieze and the appointment of Henry Carter Adams, H. Tuttle and T. H. Johnson to the Faculty (undated) (Box 44)
    - Construction Proposal, 1907 (Box 44)
    - Executive Committee, 1878-1880 (Box 44)
    - Dental School, Petitions To Establish and Correspondence, 1865-1880 (Box 44)
    - Faculty, memoranda to, 1887-1888 (Box 44)
    - Farnsworth, Elon (letter re powers of board), 1843 (Box 44)
    - Finance Committee, 1872-1882 (Box 44)
    - Fine Arts program (resolution discussing Alvah Bradish and development of fine arts program) (Box 44)
      (filed with outsize)
    - Founding date of University of Michigan, papers, 1928 (Box 44)
    - Geology, Department of (communications from W. H. Pettee and Alexander Winchell) (Box 44)
    - Gift and Trust Fund History, 1924 (Box 44)
    - "Inside Stuff," humorous skit depict Regents proceedings, circa 1920-1925 (Box 44)
    - Kearsley, Jonathan, court action against university, 1850-1851 (Box 44)
    - Legislature
      - Program, 1921 (Box 44)
      - Correspondence re., 1921 (Box 45)
      - "Non-resident" students, 1921 (Box 45)
    - Mathematics, Department of, 187?, 1880; 1882 (Box 45)
      (re. salary and personnel matters)
    - Medical Building, 1864 (Box 45)
    - Michigan Union Study, 1969 (Box 45)
    - Mines, School of (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous
      (reports from William Pettee, 1876-1879 and collected extracts from regents' proceedings)
      - Undated (Box 45)
      - 1817-1837, 3 folders (Box 45)
      - 1840 (Box 45)
      - 1842, 1853 (Bequest of property from the Association for the Promotion of Female Education) (Box 45)
      - 1867-1869 (Box 45)
      - 1870 (Box 45)
      - 1871 (Box 45)
      - 1874-1876 (Box 45)
      - 1877-1878 (Box 45)
        (include 1878 report from William Jenney)
      - 1879 (Box 45)
      - 1880 (Box 45)
      - 1881 (Box 45)
      - 1882 (Box 45)
        (includes papers re: microscopy course)
      - 1883 (Box 45)
      - 1884 (Box 45)
      - 1885 (Box 45)
      - 1886 (Box 45)
      - 1887 (Box 45)
      - 1889-1898 (Box 45)
      - 1924-1928 (Box 45)
      - 1925-1935, 7 folders (Box 45)
      - 1970 (Box 45)
    - Motor vehicle regulation (Box 45)
    - Newspaper reports of Regents meetings, index to, 1852-1863 (Box 45)
    - Palmer Field, 1910-1928 (Box 45)
    - President, selection of, 1925; 8 folders (Box 45)
    - Property, sale of "University lot,", 1858 (Box 45)
    - Regents, compiled list of, 1949-1980 (Box 45)
    - Report on Faculty Evaluation made to Regents' Committee on Educational Policies, 1943 (Box 45)
    - Rose-Douglas controversy on, 1875-1880
      - Transcripts of Testimony (Box 45)
      - Transcripts of Testimony (Box 46)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 46)
      - General material
        - undated (Box 46)
        - 1875-1876 (Box 46)
        - 1877 (Box 46)
        - 1878 (Box 46)
        - 1879-1880 (Box 46)
      - Evidence, 12 folders (Box 46)
        (including check stubs, timebooks, vouchers, and laboratory tickets)
      - Evidence, 20 folders (Box 47)
    - South College, contract to erect, 1847 (Box 47)
    - U.S. Centennial Exhibition, 1877 (Box 47)
    - Veterans' Hospital
      - Reason to build in Ann Arbor, 1917 (Box 47)
      - Location of in Ann Arbor, 1948-1952 (Box 47)
    - Wade (James H.) alleged fraud investigation, 1908-1909 (Box 47)
    - Young Men's Society of Detroit v. the Regents, undated (Box 47)
  - 1949-1969
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1957-1967 (Box 67)
    - Committee on Communications Media and University Council (Wright Committee), 1968 (Box 67)
    - Cordish, Joel, 1968-1969 (Box 67)
    - Council of Michigan College Presidents, 1963 (Box 67)
    - Cummiskey, E.A., 1958; 1966 (Box 67)
    - Detroit, City of, Advisory Committee on Hospitals of Detroit Commission on Community Relations, 1961-1968 (Box 67)
    - Dow, W.G., 1964-1965 (Box 67)
    - Emeriti Census, 1957-1963 (Box 67)
    - Flag (University) Descriptions, 1958-1971 (Box 67)
      (see also Walter J. Gores and Box 92)
    - Ford Foundation, 1958-1964 (Box 67)
    - Ford Motor Company Fund, 1958-1964 (Box 67)
    - Gift Receiving Office, 1964-1968; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Goebel, Regent Paul G., 1961-1970 (Box 67)
    - Gores, Walter J. (see also Flag Descriptions and Box 92), 1965 (Box 67)
    - Hart, Carrye and Abraham S. Fund, 1962; 1965 (Box 67)
    - Hatcher, President Harlan, 1951-1969 (Box 67)
      (scattered dates)
    - Hildebrandt, Herbert W., 1966-1970 (Box 67)
    - Hoyt, C.J., 1949-1950 (Box 67)
    - Kellogg Foundation, 1958-1966 (Box 67)
    - Kenny, Sister Elizabeth Foundation, 1961-1964 (Box 67)
    - Kipke, Harry G. (Box 67)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1960-1963 (Box 67)
    - Lamberson, Frank and Edith Scholarship Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 67)
    - Lewis, Henry C. Collection, 1963-1964 (Box 67)
    - Lewis, James A. (Vice-President for Student Affairs), 1963-1964 (Box 67)
    - Little, Clarence Cook, 1968-1969 (Box 67)
    - Matthaei, Regent Frederick C., Jr., 1967-1971 (Box 67)
    - Merck Company Foundation, 1964 (Box 67)
    - Michigan Citizens Committee on Higher Education, 1965 (Box 67)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council for Public Higher Education, 1962-1965 (Box 67)
    - Michigan Higher Education Assistance Authority, 1962 (Box 67)
    - Michigan, State of, Department of Education, 1969-1971 (Box 67)
    - Mooney, Nina C. Estate, 1964 (Box 67)
    - Nance, Willis D., 1964 (Box 67)
    - National Merit Scholarship, 1965-1966; 1968 (Box 67)
    - National Science Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 67)
    - Nilsson, Deanna, 1967 (Box 67)
    - Osborn, Mrs. Chase S., 1962-1968 (Box 67)
    - Parke, Davis & Company, 1958-1965 (Box 67)
    - Power, Regent Eugene B., 1958-1969 (Box 67)
    - Presidential Selection Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 67)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1958-1964 (Box 67)
    - Sesquicentennial, 1963-1965 (Box 67)
    - Sloan, Alfred P. Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 67)
    - Speaker Policy, 1962-1964 (Box 67)
    - Student Affairs, 1961-1966 (Box 67)
    - Tecumseh Products Company, 1961-1964 (Box 68)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H., Jr., 1963-1966 (Box 68)
    - Visiting Committees, 1962 (Box 68)
    - Walter, Erich A., 1960-1967 (Box 68)
    - Wheat, Renville, 1959-1964 (Box 68)
    - Whitney, John Hay Foundation, 1956-1962 (Box 68)
    - Willow Run Association for Neighborhood Development, 1965-1966 (Box 68)
  - Ca, 1954-1983
    - All-Campus Compiled Code (as of October 1972), 2 folders (Box 108)
    - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1976-1977; 1980; 1982-1983 (Box 108)
    - Booth Newspapers vs. The University of Michigan Board of Regents (May 19, 1978) (Box 108)
    - Clippings (1970 1982) (Box 108)
    - Ex-Officio Regents (poster, draft and final copy) (Box 108)
    - Felch, Regent Alpheus, 1973 (Box 108)
    - Ford, Gerald R. Library, 1978 (Box 108)
    - Gifts for the President's house, 1976 (Box 108)
    - History of the University of Michigan Regents, by Regent Deane Baker, 1983 (Box 108)
    - Laro, David (Box 108)
    - Lindemer, Larry, appointment (Box 108)
    - Minutes of Regents' Conferences, 1954-1966; 3 folders (Box 108)
    - The Regents of the University of Michigan and their Predecessors (draft booklet and cover design) (Box 108)
    - State of Michigan Senate Committee to Investigate Campus Disorders and Student Unrest (Parts 1 and 2), February 1970 (Box 108)
    - Suggested Reorganization of the Bylaws of the Board of Regents, March 1966 (Box 108)
    - Summary of the Degrees and Awards Conferred by the University of Michigan (booklet), 1845-1959 (Box 108)
  - Ca, 1958-2006
    - Correspondence, January 2001 (Box 175)
    - Correspondence, March 2005-November 2005; 9 folders (Box 175)
    - Correspondence, January 2006-December 2006; 13 folders (Box 175)
    - Sarah Goddard Power, 1974-1986; 2 folders (Box 175)
    - President James Duderstadt, 1988-1996 (Box 175)
    - Orientation Materials (Box 176)
      - Affirmative Action and New Regents (Box 176)
      - Financial (Box 176)
      - Handouts (Box 176)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research (Box 176)
      - Office of the Provost (Box 176)
      - Planning, 1996-1999 (Box 176)
      - University Health System (UHS), 3 folders (Box 176)
    - Review of the Code of Student Conduct, 1 volumes (Box 176)
    - Bylaws Revisions, sections 1.01-11.041 (Box 177)
      (organized by section)
    - Bylaws Revisions, sections 11.05-14.07 (organized by section) (Box 178)
    - Bylaws (Box 179)
      - Bylaws of the Regents, 1958 (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1962 (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1963 (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1964 (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1965 (Box 179)
      - Regent's Bylaws, 1966 (Box 179)
      - Suggested Reorganization of the Bylaws of the Board of Regents, March 1966; 2 folders (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws-Revision, July 1967 (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1967; 3 folders (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1968 (Box 179)
      - Policy Org, 1973-1974 (Box 179)
      - Policy File Revision, 1977 (Box 179)
      - Check Sheets (Box 179)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1970 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1971 (Box 180)
      - Bylaws-Chapter II also Dearborn and Fling Chancellors, 1970 (Box 180)
      - Bylaws-Revisions Flint and Dearborn, 1972 (Box 180)
      - May 1972-Rev. on Chapt. II, June 1972 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1973; 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws Decision Making Study in Schools & Colleges, 1974 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws Architecture Questionnaire, 1974 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws 1975-Revised (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1976 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws 1977-Revised (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1978 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws, 1980 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws 1981-Revised, 2 folders (Box 180)
        (contains tape)
      - Regents' Bylaws, March 1981 (Box 180)
      - Regents' Bylaws 1982-revisions (Box 180)